# **MEYLIANA PRATAMA**

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## May,24 1982

pratamamp@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/mpratama

Limo.Depok,West Java

081219090727

github/pratamamp

# PROFILE 💄

Hello! I am Pratama, a 38 year old Software Developer based in Depok, Indonesia. I am experienced on backend web, API, and interactive application. Skilled PHP, Javascript, Actionscript and Delphi. Bachelor Degree of University of Satya Negara Indonesia focused in Information Technology.

## **EDUCATION**



2000 - 2007 Satya Negara Indonesia University

Bachelor Degree with Information Tech-

1997 - 2000 SMU Keluarga Widuri

High school degree with science major

### **EXPERIENCE**



Oct 2019 - Current

Software Developer - Telesat System Integrator

Create and build integrated system with telco API for content provider system application/web based

Oct 2016 - Oct 2018

Web Developer - Codigo Cyberlin Metadata

Create and maintenance new website application, API for mobile application. System Analyst and

Aug 2014 - Sep 2016

Web Developer - Bisnis Indonesia Sibertama

Create and maintenance new website application

Feb 2011 - Jul 2014

Flash Developer - MNC Okezone

Interactive flash programming banner and game activity, Video Animation maker

### KNOWLEDGE 🌣



PHP frameworks Javascript stack (node, reactjs, leaflet, phaser, d3)

Git

geo spasial

Mobile (React Native)

#### **SPECIALITY**



Web Development

System Analyst

Interactive Application

**INTEREST** 



Otomotif **Embedded System**